Guide to the Daisy Aldan Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- December 2000 Acquisition, 1940-1989; Series XIX; 50; (64 boxes) + 4 broadside folders, 5 art objects
  - Writings
    - Writings by Aldan
      - "Of Arrows and Vectors" (Box 49)
      - "On Freidrich Keisler" (Box 49)
      - "On the Mysteries of Eleusis" (Box 49)
      - "Once Upon an El," film narration script, typescript (carbon) (Box 49)
      - Or Learn to Walk on Water (Box 49)
      - "Out of the Darkness" (Box 50)
      - Poetry and Consciousness (Box 50)
      - "The Precious Gems in New Jerusalem" (Box 50)
      - "Psyche and Eros" (Box 50)
      - "Report For Contemporary Drama: The Irish Theater" (Box 50)
      - "Saul Bellow: An Interview" (Box 50)
      - "A Seasonal Festival" (Box 50)
      - "Selected Poems" (Box 50)
      - "Some Early Writings and Notes" (Box 50)
      - "Some Essays and Other Writings" (Box 50)
      - "Some Lectures", 3 (Box 50)
      - "Sophronials Odd" (Box 50)
      - "Stationary" (Box 50)
      - Stones, 5 (Box 51)
      - "The Story of Claudelina", 2 (Box 51)
      - "Sunset" (Box 51)
      - "Ten Poems" (Box 51)
      - "To A Guanajuanto Baby" (Box 51)
      - "Valley of Unrest" (Box 51)
      - Verses for the Zodiac, 4 (Box 51)
      - "Walt Whitman: Poet of the Sublime", 3 (Box 51)
    - Translations
      Arranged alphabetically by author.
      Translated into English by Aldan. Translation collaborations are noted.
      - Adamov, Arthur. "Ping Pong", 8 (Box 52)
      - Goethe, Johann Wolfgang. "Faust" (Box 52)
      - Kleist, Heinrichvon. "Penthesilia", 9 (Box 52)
      - Mallarmé, Stéphane. "A Throw of Dice Never Will Abolish Chance", 5 (Box 53)
      - Mallarmé, Stéphane. "To Purify the Words of the Tribe", 7 (Box 53)
      - Mallarmé, Stéphane. "Poems", 3 (Box 53)
      - Maresca, Francesca. "The Face" with Ingeborg Maresca, 2 (Box 54)
      - Sodergran, Edith. "Poems", 8 (Box 54)
      - Steffan, Albert. "Barrabas", 6 (Box 54)
      - Steffan. Albert. "Barrabas" (Box 55)
      - Steffan, Albert. "Climb Parnassus and Behold!", 3 (Box 55)
      - Steffan, Albert. "The Death Experience of Manes" with Elly Havas Simons, 2 (Box 55)
      - Steffan, Albert. "On the Mysteries of Eleusis" (Box 55)
      - Steffan, Albert. "Winds/What You Whine/Is Woe" (Box 55)
      - Steffan, Albert. "Works etc.", 5 (Box 55)
      - Steiner, Rudolf. "The Foundation Stone Meditation", 2 (Box 56)
      - Steiner, Rudolf. "The Twelve Harmonies", 3 (Box 56)
      - Steiner, Rudolf. "Selected Translations" (Box 56)
      - Steiner, Rudolf. Poems (Box 56)
      - Steiner, Rudolf. "The Foundation Stone Meditation" (Box 56)
      - Tardieu, Jean. "The Creature of Time" (Box 56)
      - "Spanish Poets Today", 4 (Box 56)
      - "Spanish and French Poems" (Box 56)
      - Unidentified translations by Aldan, 8 (Box 56)
    - Notebooks and Diaries
      - Notebooks and diaries, 1934-1964; 30 (Box 57)
      - Notebooks and diaries, 1964-1968; 21 (Box 58)
      - Notebooks and diaries, 1968-1973; 31 (Box 59)
      - Notebooks and diaries, 1973-1979; 21 (Box 60)
      - Notebooks and diaries, 1980-1984; 20 (Box 61)
      - Notebooks and diaries, 1985-1993; 27 (Box 62)
      - Notebooks and diaries, 1995-2000, undated; 22 (Box 63)
    - Writings of Others
      - Aldan, Perry. Manuscripts, 6 (Box 64)
      - Aldan, Perry. "Pandora's Box: Gambling Scams Revealed", 1993 (Box 64)
      - Barrone, Dennis. Interview of Daisy Aldan (Box 64)
      - Bottero, Maria. Writings on Keisler, 2 (Box 64)
      - Chekov, M. Autobiography (Box 64)
      - Cohen, Diana. "Daisy Aldan: Poet" (Box 64)
      - Cohen, Diana. "Poetry and Eurythmy" interview with Daisy Aldan (Box 64)
      - Cohen, Diana. "The Written Laugh: Humorous Drawings" (Box 64)
      - Cohen, Diana. "Somewhere" (Box 64)
      - Grilikhes, Alexandra. "The Blue Scar" (Box 64)
      - [Kagri?], Laura. "Trilogy" (Box 64)
      - Markale, Jean. "Montsegur et l'enigme Cathare" photocopy (Box 64)
      - Miller, William R. Essays and school papers (Box 64)
      - Peacher, Georgiana. "Mary Stuart's Ravishment Descending Time," typescript photocopy (Box 64)
      - Perez, Paul. "Pandora's Box: Gambling Scams Revealed", 4 (Box 65)
      - Richards, Mary Caroline. "Atlantic Crossing" (Box 65)
      - Rippmann-Schmulowitz, Rea-Marianne. "Der Auferstehende Gott in den Vorahnungen der Voelker" (Box 65)
      - Roboz, Steven. "The Holy Grail from the Works of Rudolf Steiner" (Box 65)
      - Sands, Geronimo. "Carl Sandburg's World," correspondence, printed material, photographs (Box 65)
      - Spencer, Sylvia. "The Radiant Tree" (Box 65)
      - Steffen, Albert. "On the Art of Drama" (Box 65)
      - Steffen, Albert. "The Fall of the Antichrist Drama" (Box 65)
      - Upton, Elaine. "Edge of the Season" (Box 65)
      - "For Lois On Her 35th Birthday" (Box 65)
      - Poems from young students of Daisy Aldan's classes on Poets in Public Service (Box 65)
      - Poems inspired by "A House Aflame," by Daisy Aldan (Box 65)
    - Unsorted and Unidentified Writings
      - Book Reviews, 3 (Box 66)
      - Fiction (Box 66)
      - Notes, 13 (Box 66)
      - Poems, 17 (Box 67)
      - Poems, 20 (Box 68)
      - Poems, 11 (Box 69)
      - Research material on Anaïs Nin and Stéphane Mallarmé, 9 (Box 69)
      - Research material on Shakespeare, 3 (Box 70)
      - School papers and notebooks, 10 (Box 70)
      - Short stories, 2 (Box 70)
      - Speech notes (Box 70)
      - Verse translation application (Box 70)
      - Unidentified and unsorted writings, 16 (Box 71)
      - Unidentified and unsorted writings, 4 (Box 72)
  - Other Papers
    - Personal Papers
      - Daisy Aldan on Great Jones Street, 2 (Box 73)
      - Radio play scripts, 3 (Box 73)
      - Announcements for readings and lectures (Box 73)
      - Interviews and articles about Daisy Aldan (Box 73)
      - Copyrights and notices (Box 73)
      - Financial papers (Box 73)
      - Hunter College Hall of Fame certificate (Box 73)
      - Aetna Healthcare plan documents (Box 73)
      - Observations, letters of praise for Daisy Aldan teaching at High School of Art and Design (Box 73)
      - Personal and professional correspondence and other papers (Box 73)
      - Work records and teaching licenses (Box 73)
      - Certificates (Box 73)
      - Small Press Center newsletter and calendars (Box 73)
      - Poetry and education awards (Box 73)
    - Photographs
      - Aldan, Daisy, circa 1940-1980; 9 (Box 74)
      - Merasca, Ingeborg (Box 74)
      - Malanga, Gerard (Box 74)
      - Meza, Louise (Box 74)
      - Miller, Richard (Box 74)
      - Petroff, Olga (Box 74)
      - Family, 2 (Box 74)
      - Friends, 3 (Box 74)
      - Anaïs Nin - Celebration, Westbeth, 1976 (Box 74)
      - Book Fair, Washington, D. C., 1981 (Box 74)
      - Donnell Library reading with Ruth Whitman and Edward Field, circa 1968 (Box 74)
      - International Women's Festival, 1975 (Box 74)
      - Readings (Box 74)
      - Poems from India reading in India (Box 74)
      - PSA 1963 reading (Box 74)
      - Reading at Great Neck Library, 1972 (Box 74)
      - Rehearsal for Great Neck Art Center, Spanish Poetry Today (Box 74)
      - WBAI International, 1977 (Box 74)
      - Fordham University workshop, 1978 (Box 74)
      - Folder Editions (Box 74)
      - Travel photos, [Ergodie?], Isola (Box 74)
      - Isola (Box 74)
      - Ireland (Box 74)
      - [Forest Hills?], 1970s-1980s (Box 74)
      - Questa, New Mexico, 1982 (Box 74)
      - Tortola, 1980 (Box 74)
      - Photograph albums, 1988-1989; 2 (Box 74)
      - Photograph albums, 1989, undated; 3 (Box 75)
      - Postcards (Box 75)
      - Unsorted photographs, 17 (Box 75)
      - Unidentified film and negatives (Box 75)
      - Film splicing tape (Box 75)
      - Color slides of travel, lectures, and friends, 15 (Box 76)
      - Empty metal slide box (Box 76)
      - Printed material removed from slide box (Box 76)
      - Box of 35mm film rolls (2 rolls) (Box 76)
    - Printed Material
      - Folder, no. 1-4, 1953-1956; 10 (Box 77)
      - Folder, no. 3-4, 1955-1956; 3 (Box 78)
      - Dialogue, no. 2, 1984; 1 (Box 78)
      - The Destruction of Cathedrals and Other Poems, by Daisy Aldan. Inscribed by the author "For Dr. [Lipsett?] with deepest regards", 1963 (Box 78)
      - Seven: seven; poems and photographs, by Daisy Aldan and Stella Snead. Signed by the author, 1965 (Box 78)
      - Barrabas, by Albert Steffan, 1949 (Box 78)
      - Christina's World Im(media)cy Poemworks, by Gerard Malanga (Box 78)
      - Prints of poets (Box 78)
      - Zodiac, by Arne Pjedsted Salomonsen (Box 78)
      - Lebenszusammenhänge, by Jochen Bockemühl (Box 78)
      - Unsorted printed material, 7 (Box 78)
    - Artwork and Objects
      - Baia 8mm and 16mm film viewer/splicer (Box 79)
      - "Hagon" slide viewer (Box 79)
      - Dried flowers (Box 80)
      - Sketchbooks, 4 (Box 80)
      - Drawings and paintings, 16 (Box 80)
      - Drawings and paintings, 17 (Box 81 (Oversize))
      - Drawings and paintings, 7 (Box 82 (Oversize))
      - Portraits, 30 (Box 83 (Oversize))
      - Charcoal and pastel drawings, 7 (Box 84 (Oversize))
      - Watercolor paintings (Box 85 (Oversize))
      - Bust of Daisy Aldan by George Boutzky (Box 86 (Art))
      - Tall box of book plates (Box 87 (Art))
      - Abstract painting (Box 88 (Art))
      - Painting of an angel standing in a bed of flowers (Box 89 (Art))
      - Photograph of Daisy Aldan's mother on chaise lounge (Box 90 (Art))
      - Artwork (Box 91(Broadside))
      - Artwork (Box 92(Broadside))
      - Artwork (Box 93(Broadside))
  - Audiovisual Materials
    - Film
      Boxes 94-97: Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Once Upon an El, original color 8mm reel, 15 minutes, 1955; 1; 8mm motion picture film (Box 94)
        Sound is on separate reel-to-reel tapes in Box 98
        Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Various films, 7; 16mm motion picture film (Box 95)
      - Various films, 19; 8mm motion picture film (Box 95)
      - "Once Upon an El, copy, sequences have been rearranged (rough cuts)", 1955; 1; 8mm motion picture film (Box 95)
      - "Original footage of 'El' (not used)", 1955; 1; 8mm motional picture film (Box 95)
      - Various films, 28; 8mm motion picture film (Box 96)
      - Various films, 1; 16mm motion picture film (Box 97)
      - Various films, 24; 8mm motion picture film (Box 97)
    - Sound recordings
      - Reel-to-reel tapes
        Boxes 98-105: Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
        - Once Upon an El, narrative, 1955; 1; 00:41:26; A high amount of hum can be heard on the tape. (Box 98, Item barcode 39002104508982)
        - Once Upon an El, sound tapes, 1955; 1; This audiotape reel is blank. It has not been digitized. (Box 98, Item barcode 39002104508974)
        - Modern Dance Music, 1966; 20 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091392879)
          A written message on the audiotape reel's cover reads: with our love Miss Aldan, jan.
          Another message reads: To my mother; with your eyes i am conscious of all time (passing), love your son, taz
        - Daisy Aldan from Love Poems and Of Arrows and Vectors, 1972 January; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091392887)
          track speed: 7 1/2 per second
        - Sylvia Spencer poems, 1960; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091392895)
        - E. Finfer, 1960; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091392903)
        - Ruth Lisa Schechler poems, 1969 March 21; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091392911)
        - Part of Lillian Kiesler, undated; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091392929)
        - Miller [?] Daisy Aldan, 1963 March 15; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091392937)
          speed 3 3/4, monophonic
        - Daisy Aldan, Annis Vin, Serge Gavronsky, 1968 March; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091392945)
        - Poems and "Un Comp De Dés", 1960; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091392952)
        - Programs on poetry with Dave Ossman, guest: Jean Fanchette, 1960; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091392960)
        - Surrealism II, Sandra Hochman and Daisy Aldan, undated; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091392978)
          7 1/2 speed, time: 28 minutes
        - Long John Program - Wor / Daisy Aldan Contemporary poetry / A[?] Folder: American, Poems and Drawing, undated; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091392986)
        - Long John Wor / Daisy Aldan, Reel 2, undated; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091392994)
        - [Milre?], 1965; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091393000)
        - Storm de Hirsch poems, 1960 March 12; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091393018)
        - Of Arrows and Vectors and Love Poems of Daisy Aldan, Part I, 1972; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091393026)
          full track, speed: 7 1/2
        - Of Arrows and Vectors and Love Poems, Part II, undated; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091393034)
          monophonic, full track, speed 7 1/2
        - Daisy Aldan, French lecture, 1961 October 26; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091393042)
        - Daisy Aldan, Maison Franceise, French Poetry, present tense, undated; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091393059)
          3 3/4 speed
        - Anais Nin, Daisy Aldan "Coup De Des", February 8; 1 (Box 99, Item barcode 39002091393067)
        - Swedish Literature for Americans, Anais Nin & Daniel Yort, undated; 1; 00:36:14 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509113)
          A note included with the audiotape reel reads: Bunny, Could you check this? Anais thought [?] might remove some [?]??? Thanks, Bob
        - Record 3, Long John Wor, 1960 February 9; 1; 01:04:14; Program begins and ends abruptly. Program is distorted at times. There is a high amount of hum at 50:56 until the end of the tape. A note found with this audiotape reel reads: Back of this tape (i.e. on track 2), the final portion of broadcast is recorded. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509121)
          A note included with the audiotape reel dated 1960-02-11 reads: Fragile. Handle with Care! This is the literary history of tomorrow.
          Restricted fragile material.
        - The Racial Question, undated; 1; 00:07:22; Static and a high amount of hum can be heard. High background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509139)
        - Daisy Aldan: reading from Stones, (empty reel) (Box 100)
        - Character Voices, (empty reel) (Box 100)
        - Innovators, 1961 October 18; 1; 01:06:08; The program ends abruptly. Hum and static can be heard on the tape. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509147)
          French, good recording
        - Chapter 82 of Marguerite Young's Miss MacIntosh My Darling, Daisy Aldan reading, 1975 January 21; 1; 00:57:21 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509154)
        - French Poetry, Present Tense, 1963 February 16; 1; 00:33:41 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509162)
        - Anais Nin interview from film, 1963 June; 1; 00:30:23; High background noise and static can be heard on the tape. The program is recorded at a very high level. The program is distorted at about 30:24 until the end of the tape. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509170)
          A note found with this audiotape reel reads: "Contemporary Spanish Poetry", Daisy Aldan & Tana De Gomez. A typewritten note, dated 1959-03-17 from Daisy Aldan to Anais Nin is included with this audiotape reel. It reads: Dear Anais Nin, Thanks so much for your letter. I still feel bad about the books, and one of the reasons I haven't pursued Clara further is that I don't know her address out of town where she moved some time ago. One of these days, I will try to find out if Jason has a studio in New York and as soon as I do, I'll let you know. I also feel terrible that you expected to hear from me and didn't. When you get to know me better, you will see that thoughtlessness of that kind is not part of my nature. First, you went to California, then I went off on an extended trip to Europe, Greece, Africa, and so on. Then, I was so involved in all kinds of things...and so it went. Forgive me. As for the thesis, I hope to complete it this year. In any case, I think we ought to know each other better since we are both involved in similar projects and interests. Of course, you may have my mailing list - I have an excellent one now. I cannot, however, let it out of my hands at this moment. But you may feel free to come up here at any time and copy it, if you wish. Unless you have another idea. Perhaps you can spend a few hours one day soon. Simply come, make yourself at home and copy. I know how tedious it is. I have wasted and wastedd hours on such ugly details...but how well you must understand all the little things involved in running one's own press. Thanks for offering yours. One of these days, I hope I may come and copy it. Yes, I purchased a copy of your new HOUSE OF INCEST as soon as it came out. I met Val Telberg at Nell "laine's party (I had known him before), and he told me about it. The next day I picked it up at the Eighth Street Book Store. When we meet (you notice I say when, for it seems inevitable), you will tell me about purchasing your other books. I am enclosing a check for sbuscription to TWO CITIES at 40 percent discount. Under separate cover I am sending you copies of FOLDER and the COUP DE DES. I hope you enjoy them. I am no longer publishing the magazine as a magazine, but plan to publish only books. Therefore the new book of American poems and drawings will be called A NEW FOLDER. The manuscript is complete so at this moment it would be unwise to send the poems you receive to me. If YOU have any poetry of your own, however, I'd like to include you. Perhaps a prose poem. Let me know soon, for it means making room for it. I have these extra few days for I am waiting for the introduction which Wallace Fowlie is doing. I look forward to hearing from you. At any rate, come to tea or some such thing. Do let me know when you are free to do so. I remember our meeting with great pleasure. Cordially, Daisy Aldan
        - Serge Gavronski: Lecture Ecola Libre Des [?] The Innovators, 1961 October 18; 1; 00:51:11; A hum can be heard on the tape. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509188)
          Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
        - A Throw of the Dice, 1963 February 16; 1; 00:38:52; speed 7 1/2; time 39:30 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509196)
        - Surrealism I, Sandra Hochman and Daisy Aldan, undated; 1; 00:33:24 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509204)
        - Anais Nin reading from Collages ?, undated; 1; 00:10:58; A second program can be heard in the background at the beginning of the program. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509212)
        - Innovators in French Poetry, Daisy Aldan and Anais Nin, 1963 October 10; 1; 00:36:28 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509220)
        - Sound in Poetry, Daisy Aldan and Anais Nin, 1963 February 16; 1; 00:25:14; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509238)
        - Innovators, lecture and reading by Daisy Aldan, undated; 1; 00:50:23; Hum can be heard on the tape. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509246)
        - Albert Steffen talks about Rudolf Steiner and poems, undated; 1; 00:37:43 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509253)
        - Racial Question, undated; 1; 00:13:09; Static can be heards on the tape. There is a high amount of hum that can be heard from about 07:33 until the end of the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509261)
        - Empty?, undated; 1; This tape was not digitized due to damage (oxide flaking). (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509279)
        - Living Theatre reading from A New Folder, 1959 June 12; 1; 01:04:13; The program begins abruptly. The volume fluctuates throughout the program. The program is distorted at times. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002104509295)
        - Daisy Aldan reading from her book Stones: Folder Editions / Tazwell Thompson reading Aldan's: Verses for the Zodiac, 1975 January 19; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392671)
          7 1/2 speed
        - The Racial Question, Tazwell Tompson without music, undated; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392689)
          7.5 speed
        - Aldan at the Free Music store, The Woman's Day Program, 1975 March 8; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392697)
        - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392705)
        - Contemporary Spanish Poetry, Daisy Aldan and Tana De Gomez, 1963 October 10; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392713)
          7 1/2 speed, time 36:30
        - Scenes from Shakespeare, 1963 February 16; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392721)
          7 1/2 speed, time 28:30; dub
        - "Un Coup De Dés", Fanchette and Aldan, undated; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392739)
        - "Daisy Aldan on Great Jones '81", 1973 January; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392747)
        - Poetry reading, 1972 February 2; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392754)
          Daisy Aldan reads a selection from her 1971 book of poems, "Breakthrough". it concludes with a reading of a portion of her 1971 translation of Albert Steffen's "The Death Experience of Manes".
          3 3/4 speed, full 2-track, 4-track
        - Poetry workshop, 1975 March 18; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392762)
        - Ella Heyde Alt, 1974 October 20; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392770)
        - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392788)
        - "El", undated; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392796)
          Mixed track.
        - Daisy Aldan reads poems from India, 1970 May 13; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392804)
          The opening cue is: This is Pulsebeat 70..." The closing cue is: "...played by Ravi Shankar".
        - "Today's World", 1972 December 3; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392812)
          speed: 7 1/2
        - Selected poems of Albert Steffen translated from German by Daisy Aldan, undated; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392820)
        - Reading from Of Arrows and Vectors and Love Poems, Folder Editions, 1972 January; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392838)
        - Albert Steffen reading with music, 1972 January 26; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392846)
          2-channel mono, 7 1/2 ips
        - Reading from selected poems of Albert Steffen, 1972; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392853)
          2-channel mono dub, 7 1/2 ips
        - Untitled, 1975 February 9; 1 (Box 101, Item barcode 39002091392861)
          Reel 2 of 2, dub
        - Daisy Aldan's Mother, Esther Finper, 1960; 1 (Box 102, Item barcode 39002091393075)
        - Calligraphy Poetry Series, "Journey" - Daisy Aldan, "Movable Pars" - Ruth Schechter, "The [?] Beads - Virginia Brady Young, 1970 April 25; 1 (Box 102, Item barcode 39002091393083)
        - From "Breakthrough Poems" by Daisy Aldan, 1969; 1 (Box 102, Item barcode 39002091393091)
          full track, speed: 7.5, with echo
        - Sound in Poetry, May 3; 1 (Box 102, Item barcode 39002091393109)
        - Reading by Daisy Aldan taped by Diana Cohen, undated; 1 (Box 102, Item barcode 39002091393117)
          3 3/4 speed, runtime: 50 minutes
        - AH 1, Lecture 2, undated; 1 (Box 102, Item barcode 39002091393125)
        - Aldan, single, undated; 1 (Box 102, Item barcode 39002091393133)
          7 1/2 speed, 8 min.
        - Selections from WPAI, 1972 December 10; 1 (Box 102, Item barcode 39002091393141)
        - Poems from "The Destruction of Cathedrals" read by Daisy Aldan, 1962; 1 (Box 102, Item barcode 39002091393158)